Every time the rain no longer
falls and I see the sky?
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger!
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do.
My voyage will not end.
No matter what's next!
I'm walking straight ahead.
So let's go!
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's all on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything Will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me Push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through.
No matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go!
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
What I hope you're away from me?
I know the future's there for us to see.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
He's...
He can't be.
He's no!
Oh, my God, you know?
It's in your head! Kill him!
That looks bad.
Now fire!
This just keeps getting worse.
What's next?
It's no use.
We can't stop him.
It would seem you're still
alive if only barely.
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
I won't let you lay a finger on him.
You're only delaying the
inevitable, you fool.
No one can stand up to me.
You were a warlord.
You know what I'm capable of.
No matter the cost, if I can delay you
for even a moment, then I'll be satisfied.
I'm not afraid to die!
Chief Bay Marco we got the
key guy I thought I was dead
but you saved me save it
for later unlock these cuffs
Wait, Vice Admiral, what?
What are you?
Garp!
You stay out of this, you old fool.
That's right, Sengoku.
You, you better keep holding me
like that, because if you don't,
I swear that I am going
to murder Sakazuki.
Damn it all.
I need to execute a traitor, too.
Seems my job is never done.
Jipe, get down!
Haki users, what a pain?
But you're far too late!
We're so close.
Don't give up yet!
There's still a chance.
The battle has ended,
Firefist is done for.
See for yourself?
Ace, come on.
You're okay, right? Right?
Don't worry, Ace.
I'll get you some help, Kate.
Sorry, Luffy.
I tried.
Come on!
You did great.
Thank you for trying so hard for me.
But looks like this is as far as I can go.
Forgive me.
What are you talking about?
This isn't over yet!
Somebody please, please help him!
Hurry up!
Come on, we can still save him!
Dammit, don't just
stand there, he's dying!
This way, Doctor, quick!
It's not looking good! Okay.
Oh, Straw Boy!
Hold on, Ace!
I'm here for you!
Here, I got it!
Thanks! Move!
Let me see the wound, please.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
What do you mean? Sorry?
You are a doctor, aren't you?
It's too late.
There's gotta be something!
But he's still alive!
You're not even gonna try?
We didn't come all this way to lose him!
Now you can't just give up!
It's no use!
He burned through my organs too!
This is it for me!
I can feel it!
I can feel my life slipping away!
Don't say that!
God, the fight's not over yet.
Please, we can still save you.
Don't tell me you're gonna give up now.
Not you.
That's not the big brother I know.
You remember your promise, don't you?
Say something.
If it weren't for Sabo, a certain
little brother I had to look after.
Didn't want you turning
out like me, you know?
Maybe I should have never been born.
Maybe I never deserved to
live in the first place?
Huh?
If Gold Roger had a son?
What are you talking about?
It's obvious, isn't it?
He'd end up just like his dad.
Off with his damn head!
Nah, after all the crap he
started, Roger got off too easy.
If you ask me,
I say we'd count up all the man's crimes
and prick his boy with
a needle for everyone.
Come on, I bet all the pirates
would worship that kid like a god.
We'd have to do something really nasty,
like burn him alive and
make everybody watch.
There you go.
Come on, pirates, why
don't you go join him?
They didn't probably cry
and shut him down for good.
I'm trashed just like my dad.
I should die.
Now I almost wish he didn't have a son.
I never asked to be born,
but they hated me anyway.
I can't believe you ace didn't I just tell
you to stop this I don't
care what they said.
You're just making life
harder for both of us.
Hey are you listening
to me don't hurt people.
You're gonna stop me to don
what I would have killed them
all if I could and one of these
days I'll be strong enough.
Oh yeah if you see dadan tell her I said
hello and thank her for
putting up with us too.
I never thought I'd miss a woman like her
but I guess dying does
funny things to you.
Don't say that!
You're not dying!
There is one thing that hurts.
I won't be around to see
you fulfill your dream.
That's fine.
I have faith.
You can do it.
Because you're my brother.
Do you remember that day?
Luffy, listen.
There's only one way to live life,
and that's without any regrets.
Someday, we're going to head out to
sea and live the way we want to live.
More free than anyone else.
I did it.
I lived with no regrets, even
though it ended this way.
Can't complain, huh?
Well, I can!
You can't die like this!
Sure, things could have gone
better, but it's all right.
I realized I didn't need
fame or fortune after all.
All I needed was the answer
to a single question.
At the very end, did I deserve to be born?
I will call you my son, who
we've got plenty to talk about.
Like you not killing my son.
Ace, you're my brother, damn it!
Say whatever mean stuff you want!
I'm still gonna save you!
Listen up, pirates!
Bring Ace to safety!
And once you're done with
that, destroy the Navy!
I can't raise my voice anymore, too weak.
Could you tell everyone else what
I'm about to say when I'm done?
Pops, my family, and you, Luffy,
thank you for caring
about someone like me,
who's good
for nothing.
This world never wanted.
One has such bad blood in his veins.
Thank you
for
loving me.
I don't know.
Old man
Yeah
Tell me the truth
Did I deserve to be born
Or was it just a mistake
That's not for me to say
You just keep living
And hope you find out?
Ace.
I don't know.
You didn't really think
I was dead, did you?
Yeah, well I'm not!
So stop your crying and
have some faith for once!
I promise I'm not gonna die, okay?
Not ever.
At least not as long as I've got a wussy
little brother who needs me to protect him.
Drop.
Please look after my child.
Our son's name is Goldie Ace.
It's the truth.
All it takes to become
brothers is to share some sake.
All right, from here on out,
we're honest-to
-goodness brothers.
Thank you.